[♪ theme music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, ETC. ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
ANIMALS WERE FILMED
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION AND WELFARE RULES
[♪ whimsical music playing]
Last year's blue crab festival logo
put too much emphasis on the crab,
making it look
like a fish market promotion.
I think that was a bit unfortunate.
So, Merry Design Studio
[remote clicks]
came up with a design
that portrays a festival
you can enjoy
with family, friends, and dates.
Also, the souvenirs you'll give out
to the visitors
will include the cute crab image
that we designed.
Like this.
GENERAL EVALUATION:
I DO NOT WISH TO SELECT THIS COMPANY
[sighs]
Ms. Yoo, do you like blue crabs?
Of course, I do.
I'm a blue crab killer.
I can eat about three in a sitting.
Ohh! Say there's a big one
and a small one. Which would you prefer?
Of course, I prefer a big, fleshy one.
The salty, flavorful taste
of a fat crab...
My mouth is watering already.
So, you like them big.
There's more to it than just the size.
[men laughing]
Ms. Yoo, you're not married, are you?
-No.
-Hmm.
-[clicks tongue]
-[chuckles]
Show her what's good.
She likes them big and fleshy.
He's known as the Hongju City Killer.
-Good luck with him.
-[men laughing]
-Watch yourself.
-I will.
2025 BLUE CRAB FESTIVAL
DESIGN PITCH
Sir, what you just said.
May I ask exactly what you meant?
Pardon? What did I say?
You wished me good luck.
Good luck with what, exactly?
Why don't you wrap up your presentation?
We're short on time,
so don't try to pick a fight.
I'm not picking a fight.
I just want to know
what you meant when you said--
-[man] Ms. Yoo?
-Yes?
Don't you want the job?
We wanted to give
an obscure company a project,
but who'd want to work
with someone so aggressive?
[sighs deeply]
Fine.
Don't work with me.
I refuse the job.
I'm sorry, but to be honest,
I'm picky about who I work with myself.
I might as well say this
since I won't get the job.
You there.
Yes, you. The man who just pointed.
Do you think you hold a lot of power?
You might have the advantage here,
but outside, I have the upper hand.
My taxes pay your salary.
-[scoffs]
-[men snicker]
I had no idea
my tax money ended up
in the pockets of such trash.
-[stutters] What?
-[♪ dramatic music playing]
What did you just say?
-Me?
-Yes, you.
-How old are you?
-Why would you ask my age?
-How dare she talk like that?
-Are you jealous that I'm young?
You dare take that tone with me?
-Let go of me.
-[man] Leave it.
-Do you look down on our city?
-No, Hongju City is blameless.
JAMYANG PRINT SHOP
[woman over phone] So basically,
you caused a stir and got kicked out.
Don't worry.
You're my only employee.
I'll manage to pay you somehow.
[woman] I doubt that.
We scored zero projects this month.
How will you pay this month's rent?
Did we get any inquiries
on our social platforms?
Stay on the line while I go and see.
I think we got a couple of small jobs.
2 PROJECTS UNDERWAY
Giveaways for a new butcher shop
and a logo for a Magok coffee shop.
The coffee shop owner wants to see
a portfolio before they decide.
Should we send our old herbal tea design?
Sure, will you come back to the office?
Oh, no. I have to drop by
a nearby department store
while I'm out in Euljiro.
You can finish the draft and go home.
[line disconnects]
Sir.
Could you lower
the saturation of this part
while keeping the color Pantone 213?
I lowered it already.
Yes, but the case is transparent,
so it'll look different when it's filled.
You can't mind that, too. Who will notice?
A reprint will just cost you more.
I know the difference.
I can't sell anything to a customer
if something bothers me.
You're too picky.
You'll never make a fortune doing that.
Sir.
Thank you.
[giggles]
[♪ orchestral music playing in store]
We engraved the wedding bands
with your initials.
Thanks.
The receipt, warranty card,
and raffle ticket are inside.
Thank you.
Thank you. Goodbye.
I emailed a copy
of my boyfriend's passport.
Yes, Kim Wooju.
Thank you. Bye.
That's the honeymoon booked.
WHEN WILL YOU BE DONE?
[♪ enthralling music playing]
[both breathing heavily]
I love you.
[breathing heavily]
[moaning]
-[phone vibrates]
-[chuckles softly]
[Ms. Yoo] When will you be done?
[Wooju] I'm in a meeting.
[Ms. Yoo] You're working late again today?
YOU'RE WORKING LATE AGAIN TODAY?
It must be tiresome.
-Who is it?
-[Ms. Yoo] You've got this.
-[Wooju] I love you.
-What did she say?
[both breathing heavily]
[Ms. Yoo] I was hoping to have dinner
with him.
Oh, gosh.
Sorry.
[♪ pleasant whimsical music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
EPISODE 1
ALWAYS ACCEPT AN APOLOGY
CUTE WOOJU
NEVER LET A FIGHT LAST MORE THAN A DAY
WOOJU TAKES OUT THE RECYCLING
HANDWRITE LETTERS ON ANNIVERSARIES
TAKE A MONTHLY TRIP IN KOREA
Forget the wedding and whatnot.
I wish I could call it all off.
Oh, Meri.
You can't just register your marriage
and say it's done.
-It's a hassle, but a necessary one.
-[Meri] Mom.
The problem is that there's so much to do.
I have so little money to spare,
but Wooju's mother
keeps going on about a hotel.
It's driving me up the wall.
If she has the money for a hotel wedding,
she should contribute to our rent.
Her son has a fancy degree,
and her husband's a university professor.
She has an appearance to keep up.
Try to understand. [chuckles]
Where are you?
-Did you have dinner?
-Yes.
I ate.
I'm at our new place.
I come by whenever I can
to unpack and organize stuff.
Did you have dinner, Mom?
I did. What about Wooju?
He moved in already.
He didn't call to tell you?
He must know we couldn't afford this place
without your help.
Leave it.
I gave you the money
so he'd be good to you.
Let me give you a word of caution.
Don't nag him for not having
contributed to the deposit.
You shouldn't discourage a man.
What? Why would he be discouraged?
I cater to him in every way.
I'm good wife material
that's rare these days.
You're the kid out of the two of us.
[chuckling]
Mom.
I'll make lots of money
and pay you back soo-- [gasps]
What's the matter?
It's fine.
I just stepped on something.
Mom, I'll call you back a bit later.
Bye.
What is this?
It's not my...
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ suspenseful music swells]
[music stops]
[♪ pop music playing in background]
[chuckling] I look like a model.
What about this?
It's when I played golf
with some investors.
I know that.
-A comment on that post.
-Yes.
"Sweet Jenny 97."
[♪ dramatic music playing]
-What?
-She liked every single post of yours.
SWEET_JENNY97
YOUR FACE IS ALL I SEE
You follow each other. Who is that?
[chuckles]
She's just a colleague of mine.
Didn't I mention her? I bet I did.
[clears throat]
She went to school in Hong Kong.
Did you sleep with her?
[coughs]
[chuckles nervously] Hey.
What's up with you?
Why the heck would I sleep with her?
[sighs deeply]
[earring clatters]
Then why did I find this by the bed?
What's this?
[♪ dramatic sting]
[♪ tense music playing]
Oh, I was at a company workshop
in Gangwon-do last week.
A few colleagues came by to look around.
-Colleagues?
-You see, they were dead curious.
She must have dropped it then.
I should give it back.
Last week, your department head
went fishing on Anmyeondo Island.
Your section chief
took his kids to Lotte World.
Assistant Manager Jang.
He went to the wedding
of a guy he met in the army.
The Gangwon-do workshop...
Did you and Jenny go on your own?
Sunset Resort.
Each suite has a private pool.
You were there overnight,
so I don't need to ask what went on.
What do you think?
If you keep denying it,
should I cause a scene at your office
like some soap opera?
[spits, coughing]
Hey.
[sniffles]
Fine.
I'll come clean.
I'm Adam, who fell for a snake's lies.
I partook of the forbidden fruit. So what?
-[café patrons murmuring]
-[♪ ominous sting]
"So what?"
Why do you think I did?
It was because I was under so much stress.
My investors call every day
about profit margins,
while I'm just a newbie
with a wedding coming up.
Don't you see how much is on my mind?
I was already on edge,
and you nagged me so much.
You called, texted, and bossed me about
with the wedding prep.
[laughing] I felt like I was being fried.
Am I getting married on my own? [echoes]
I work full-time, too.
-I'm busy, too!
-I know you are!
That's why I... [echoes]
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
I'm a jerk.
[café patrons gasp]
I deserve a beating!
Say a number. How many slaps?
[sighs]
I know you have a glib tongue.
But not today.
I won't let you off like that today.
Meri. Let's think rationally.
We booked a wedding hall,
got a marriage license,
and rented an apartment.
Leave me, and you'll be a divorcée
even without a wedding.
Wow, isn't that so unfair?
It is unfair!
Right? That makes zero sense.
That girl, Jenny...
She's just a fling.
And you and I will be together forever.
It was a one-time mistake,
and I ended it with her already.
[sighs wearily]
[phone vibrates]
JENNY
[Jenny] When are you coming over?
I'm waiting for you in the underwear
you got me yesterday.
Isn't it pretty?
[♪ dramatic sting]
[clears throat]
[♪ tense music playing]
It's my section chief.
About tomorrow's business trip.
Did I ever ask to see your phone?
No.
I have a bad feeling.
If I don't see this now,
I might doubt you forever and ever.
Move your hand.
What are you doing?
It was my section chief.
Let me see it.
It was my section chief, okay?
Exactly, that's why I want to see.
Why see my section chief's...
[screams]
Are you all right?
-Did he step on her hand?
-Hey.
He stomped on her hand.
-What's going on?
-Is she okay?
[Wooju] Why did you try to see my phone?
You shouldn't cross the line
however close you are with someone.
Let's see your hand.
[breathing heavily]
"The line?"
You're the one who crossed the line.
That apartment is ours,
and we're soon to be married.
You brought another woman over.
[café patrons gasp]
-No way.
-How could you do that?
[café patron 1] Is he out of his mind?
[café patrons murmuring]
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[voice shaking] For seven months
after you got your new job,
you always worked late
or had a team dinner.
You were so hard to reach.
You even forgot my birthday
and our anniversary.
I got fitted for a wedding dress on my own
because you were too busy.
I couldn't bear...
the thought of letting
our five years go to waste.
So, I told myself to ignore everything
and just marry you.
But I won't.
I think I'll divorce you one day
even if we do get married.
If it's bound to happen one day,
that might as well be today.
Meri.
[café patrons gasp]
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
[café patron 2] She actually drenched him.
-[café patron 3] Did you see that?
-[café patron 4] That was insane.
[passenger] She's pretty old, you see,
and I need to sit next to her.
-[air hostess] Is it for health concerns?
-[passenger] Yes.
Could you get him to swap with me?
[air hostess] I'll ask the gentleman
for you.
-Will you come with me?
-[passenger] Sure.
-[air hostess] Let's go.
-[passenger] Yes, thanks.
[air hostess] Sir?
Were you assigned seat 5D?
Yes.
This gentleman says
he was given a seat
apart from his elderly mother.
He'd like to know
if you could switch with him.
I'm so sorry.
My mother is very old,
and I need to assist her
during the flight.
Will you swap with me, sir?
I don't want to.
My seat is also in business class.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Sir?
Hello?
[air hostess over PA system]
We have reached our destination
at Incheon International Airport.
When opening overhead storage
after the plane stops,
please take care to ensure
nothing falls out.
Thank you.
14 HOURS PRIOR
The old hag's trying to run away
without selling the land,
so I'll sit next to her
and get her to sign the papers.
My big sister in Seoul
won't let me anywhere near Mom.
I need to get the papers signed
on the plane.
Mom could die any day now.
That's why I need the papers signed soon.
Ma'am.
Keep the land deeds until the day you die.
Don't trust your son
and hand it right over.
You can't trust anyone out there.
[grunts]
I just landed.
I'm going straight to Yangyang.
[woman over phone] You rotten fool.
Why not drop by to say hi first?
I made a video call
before I got on the plane.
It's not that I want to see you.
I picked too many zucchinis.
I can't eat it all.
Put them in the freezer.
I'll eat them when I'm back.
You never say you'll come by.
I'm scared you'll put me right to work.
Grandma, it's my first holiday
in three years.
I'll let you off just this once.
Just wait until you start work.
How can you only think about putting
your one and only grandson to work?
I spent a fortune to feed and educate you.
I have a long way to go
to make up for the tuition I invested.
You're so calculative.
A peddler's not a peddler
if they're not calculative.
Okay, fine.
Good luck with the zucchinis
and sweet potatoes while I'm away.
See you in a month.
I'll be in touch.
[chuckles]
You prepared a lot of food.
-Shall I stay and eat with you?
-No.
He survived on hamburgers
in a foreign country without his parents.
I was hoping to feed him
some home-cooked food.
[♪ upbeat pop music
playing over car stereo]
[sighs in relief]
[♪ gentle synth music playing]
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
[cat meows]
[meows]
[purrs]
[sighs]
HAPPINESS
[gasps]
[exclaims excitedly]
ONE MONTH LATER
[judge] The one-month consideration period
has ended,
and I confirm Kim Wooju
and Yoo Meri's intent to divorce.
[Meri sighs softly]
I can't believe
all the things you make me do.
Stupid me.
I shouldn't have registered our marriage
when you asked to.
It was the only way to get your mother
to pay the housing deposit.
Are you saying
she forced you against your will?
-You--
-That's not true.
[sighs deeply]
-What did your mother say?
-She didn't say anything.
I couldn't tell her I became a divorcée
before I even walked down the aisle.
Sorry.
I'll tell her later when the time's right.
I said we'd postpone the wedding
because you're busy.
Keep that in mind.
Okay.
I'll vacate the apartment,
so take your stuff.
Are you moving out?
Do you want me to live there when you...
I took out a massive loan.
You're right.
[chuckles softly]
You'll have much less debt, at least.
It's a good thing we broke up.
Sure, it's just great.
I'm so grateful I could cry.
I have much less debt.
[phone vibrating]
[whispering] Hi, Jenny.
Are you at the airport already?
Yes, I'm just about to leave.
Okay, see you soon.
[line disconnects]
[in normal voice]
I'm going somewhere on holiday.
I have to hand in our divorce decree.
Did you fill in your details?
Yes.
Thanks for submitting it for me.
Don't thank me.
I'm doing it in case you don't.
Hey, don't hate me too much.
We were
in love for a while.
[Wooju sighs wistfully]
Meri.
Live a good life.
Forget all about me.
Wooju.
Get lost.
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
Hey, you should find a good guy.
Don't wait too long.
You get over love with love!
I'm on my way now.
Darn you!
[sighs in exasperation]
HOME APPLIANCE FAIR FOR NEWLYWEDS
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
[phone vibrates]
RIZZ WEDDING HALL
THE BLUEMON HALL RESERVATION WAS CANCELED
[phone vibrates]
DREAM TRAVEL AGENTS
YOUR HONEYMOON PACKAGE WAS CANCELED
[phone vibrates]
ELLE WEDDING DRESSES
YOUR WEDDING DRESS RENTAL WAS CANCELED
[distorted laughter]
[Meri] Do clean breakups exist?
[♪ slow melancholy music playing]
[Meri sighs]
You pretend to be okay.
What's broken
can't be glued back together.
-[Wooju] Meri.
-Yes?
-I love you.
-I love you, too.
[giggles]
[inhales sharply]
I'll live well without you now.
I'll make lots of money.
I'll go on lots of trips.
I'll even go on blind dates.
[voice shaking]
I'll forget the likes of you...
I'll live...
I'll...
I'll be really busy.
[sobbing]
[continues sobbing]
Young man.
I'd grown to like you.
I'm sad to see you go.
They say those who meet must part.
Here.
-Eat it on the way.
-What's this?
Ooh!
It's corn bread.
I got it from the best place nearby.
Just for you.
How is it?
-It's good.
-[chuckles]
I should bring you some bread next time.
Bread?
My family owns the best bakery
in the whole country.
A bakery?
-Hmm.
-Oh! [chuckles]
Thanks for this.
MYUNGSOONDANG
[interviewer] Congratulations.
Myungsoondang won the President's Award
at the Industrial Day award ceremony.
How do you feel?
[interviewee] I don't have much to say,
but that I'm grateful and thankful.
[chuckles]
I appreciate the acknowledgement
that I make everything
as if it were for my own child,
using no preservatives.
I can only thank you.
[interviewer] How humble of you.
Myungsoondang is Korea's first-ever bakery
-as well as...
-Your grandma
dumps a whole load of additives
when she cooks.
-Just not in the bread.
-[camera shutter clicking]
You should, too,
since your food is horrible.
[interviewer] ...you even announced
a new beginning.
-Eat all you want.
-[interviewer] How is that going?
At the Paris Dessert Fair last year,
our hangwa was incredibly popular.
I got many inquiries
from department stores
in Paris, London, and New York,
so I plan to promote
our traditional hangwa
as a K-dessert throughout the world.
KOREA ECONOMY
[♪ feel-good music playing]
Chairwoman, can you pose
with one of your products this time?
Yes, sure.
Here you go, Chairwoman.
Get me one of our new products.
Here it is.
Will you take the photo
so the hangwa looks nicer than me?
Mom, you're not shooting a commercial.
Why not make an interview
work as well as one?
Yes, let's milk it for all it's worth.
"Make it worthwhile."
Use nice language.
I used easy language, Mom.
[snarls]
[giggling]
[photographer] One, two, three.
CHAIRWOMAN KO
WINS ANNUAL PRESIDENT'S AWARD
[slurps]
What did the coffee shop owner say?
Really?
We'll go with a cat, then.
The customer is king.
Let's put just the shop name
on the napkins
and put stickers
on the paper cups and sleeves.
Are the samples at the office?
[gasps] Oh, yes. I brought them home.
The samples...
Where did I put them?
Here they are.
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
I have to hand in our divorce decree.
Did you fill in your details?
I need to hand this in soon.
[knocking at door]
[man] Is anyone home?
[knocking continues]
Is someone in?
POLICE
Do you live here?
Yes, is something wrong?
[sighs in relief]
We meet at last.
JUNGMUN POLICE, SERVING WITH WARMTH
[Meri] A rental con?
[officer] The homeowner had left a realtor
in charge of the property
while she was abroad.
Without the realtor knowing,
their assistant got someone
to pretend to be the homeowner
and sign a fake lease with you.
What happens to me, then?
You have to move out,
or the homeowner
will report you for trespassing.
I can't move out
until I get my security deposit back.
You need to sue the people
who conned you to get that back.
[sighs]
But the fake homeowner is a vagrant
who let the scammer use his identity.
Are you saying
I might not get my money back?
[breathing heavily]
WOOJU
[line ringing]
What? A rental con?
You should've looked into it better.
Do you have rental insurance?
Why didn't you do something that basic?
My uncle?
Yes, he's at the Public Prosecutors'...
I can't ask a favor
for something like that.
Don't talk as if it has
nothing to do with you. [sighs]
I don't know anyone else to ask for help.
Is there nothing you can do?
My savings, a bank loan,
and my mom's money went into it.
-It's 300 million won.
-[clears throat]
Meri.
It does have nothing to do with me.
It's none of my business now.
We're complete strangers now.
You need to accept reality.
Will you call me
whenever something goes wrong?
It's really rude to call your ex
out of the blue like this.
I picked up this time for old time's sake,
but I won't anymore, okay?
No, wait.
-Wooju, hello?
-[line disconnects]
WOOJU
[automated voice] The phone is off.
Transferring to voicemail.
Oh, no.
What do I do?
He's right.
[breathes deeply]
We are complete strangers now.
But even so.
We only just broke up.
Is that all he could say?
I haven't even submitted
our divorce decree.
[♪ slow melancholy music playing]
If not for you,
I wouldn't even have
rented that apartment. [sighs]
And now you're turning your back on me?
What am I to do now?
[sighs]
MOM
[phone vibrating]
Hi, Mom.
Hey, Meri.
I braised some yellow croaker
and seasoned some cucumbers.
Wooju's parents haven't moved, right?
What?
You don't have to send them food.
Let's keep the good food to ourselves.
Why cook for them?
It's extra work for you.
I made a little extra while I was at it.
Cooking a bit more food
doesn't wear my hands or feet.
Just don't send them anything.
Why would you keep sending them stuff?
MERI
What's up with you?
[gasps] Do they not like my food?
No, it's not that.
There's nothing else I can do for them.
I want to do what I can for you and them.
I can only do this while I'm still able.
I don't have much longer.
My shoulders are beginning
to ache, you know.
-[chuckles]
-Mom.
I'm sorry.
What the heck?
Have you finally grown up
now that it's time to get married?
[chuckling]
Meri.
Don't think too much and go to bed.
I have to watch my favorite show. Bye.
Okay, bye.
[line disconnects]
[sighs, sniffles]
[sniffles]
CHEONGHUN 1-GA
[automated voice] You went off course.
-What?
-Rerouting.
Oh, geez.
Turn right at the next corner.
[♪ soft, gripping music playing]
WOOJU
[line ringing]
Kim Wooju, you punk.
Why did it send me this way?
My goodness...
Go straight for 150 meters and turn right.
[tires screech]
What was that?
[gasps]
Are you all right?
[softly exclaims in pain]
[sighing in exhaustion]
[slurring] I'm fine.
Are you really fine?
I'm fine. It hurts a bit, but I'm okay.
Let's go to a hospital just in case.
I'm good.
I'll give you my number, then.
See a doctor, then call me.
What a hassle.
Here you go.
Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
KIM WOOJU
"Kim Wooju"?
[♪ gripping music playing]
Yes, that's my name.
You piece of dirt.
[Kim Wooju groans]
Why did you ignore my calls?
-Me?
-[sighs]
You punk!
Do you think avoiding me will work?
Why would I avoid you? I'm not like that.
[chortles]
You're not?
Take responsibility, then.
"Take responsibility?"
Aah!
You want a settlement?
Whatever. Hand it over right now.
Fine.
How much do you want?
A hundred million won.
-A hundred million won?
-Yes, that's right.
What is wrong with you?
Do you take me for a pushover?
-You're being unreasonable.
-[exclaims]
You're the unreasonable one.
Do as I say.
-Hand it over.
-What?
It's my mom's money.
Hand it over, punk.
You're insane.
Why are you asking me
for the money to give to your mom?
[cat yowls]
Where do you think you're going?
Where are you going?
What do you think you're doing?
Get out of my car.
I won't.
[whines]
[Kim Wooju struggling]
What the...
Drive on.
My goodness.
Why are you so strong?
-Get out.
-No.
[exclaiming]
Get out. [grunts]
Come here.
-Will you stop it?
-Get out already.
Leave me alone.
-Stop it.
-[car horn blares]
Darn you.
[panting]
If you don't stop this,
I'll call the police.
Hey, you.
[grunts]
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
What are you doing now?
You can't go.
Why do you keep trying to get away?
-Is she crazy?
-Shouldn't we stop her?
You want to run away?
Hey, are you seeing this?
Should we do something?
-What's wrong with her?
-I don't know.
[grunting]
[both panting]
[Meri] Hey.
Aren't you being too hard on me?
[sniffles]
[breath trembling] You cheated on me.
What makes you think you're in the right?
-What?
-Why are you doing this to me?
[crying] Why are you making me do this?
I became a divorcée
without ever getting
to walk down the aisle.
My mom...
It will break her poor heart.
What about my mom?
I can't tell her the truth.
[continues crying]
[♪ soft melancholy music playing]
[Meri sobbing]
Mom...
[voice shaking] Mom, what should I do?
Mom... [continues sobbing]
Hey, are you all right?
You...
I don't think you are.
[sniffles]
You're...
[♪ dramatic sting]
[crying hysterically]
-It hurts!
-You...
Come here.
Help me.
Why would you...
-[groans]
-[doctor] How many did we get?
[nurse] A total of 17.
[doctor] Did we get everything?
There's one more over there.
Oh, here it is.
[surgical instruments clatter]
We're done.
Don't shower for the next two days.
I'll prescribe you
a painkiller and antibiotics.
Okay. [sniffles]
[sighs wearily]
Hey, how did it happen?
Wasn't she drunk?
She reeked of alcohol.
How could you confuse
a cactus for a stool
because you were drunk?
Sitting on a cactus must be so painful.
[♪ comical music playing]
[doctor] It'll throb for a few days,
but she'll be fine.
It's usually a job for the interns,
but I did it myself because you asked.
[chuckles] Thanks, Jingyeong.
-You were the first to come to mind.
-What?
Only when you need help?
You've been back for a month,
and you never called.
How did you know I was back?
My dad is your grandmother's doctor.
He heard it during her checkup.
Aah!
So...
Who is that woman?
Your girlfriend?
It didn't seem so.
My girlfriend?
As if she'd be my girlfriend.
She's just some drunk I met in the street.
She bumped into my car.
You did that to her?
What? Well, no.
It's a long story.
I'll tell you another time.
Do you work late all the time?
Yes, I'm preparing for a conference,
so I have to stay up for a whole week.
[yawns]
[yawning] I'm so tired.
Cover your mouth when you yawn. [scoffs]
Wooju.
I treated her, so you owe me a coffee.
A coffee?
Sounds good.
What's wrong with her?
I told her to get an X-ray.
Hey, Jingyeong.
The coffee has to wait.
Wooju.
Kim Wooju!
Couldn't he even stay for a coffee?
[yawns]
[clears throat] I could take a taxi.
And sit like that?
[chuckles softly]
You must've been so flustered earlier.
The alcohol must've made me lose my mind.
I know you thought I was a weirdo.
To be honest, I had a bad day today.
I can't go into detail
since we just met, but...
I mistook you for someone else.
You happened to have the same name.
By the way,
I don't need to get an arm X-ray.
-It was just a slight bump...
-[sunroof whirring]
[Kim Wooju exhales]
I smell the alcohol whenever you talk.
I feel dizzy.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
Excuse me. [clears throat]
I'm really sorry,
but could you pull over?
What for?
Going backwards gives me motion sickness.
Seriously?
Fine.
Thank you.
[exhales]
Are you all right?
[groans softly]
[sighs]
[♪ slow poignant music playing]
[Meri sighs]
The sun is rising.
It's like a red flower...
blooming through the dark.
[Meri sighs]
Even though my world crumbles,
the sun still rises,
and morning still comes.
There's always a way out, right?
It feels as if Mother Nature...
is giving me a message.
[stomach rumbling]
[chuckles softly]
The message must be "feed me."
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[stomach continues rumbling]
I'm the type... [clears throat]
who must eat breakfast every morning.
Would you like to get breakfast?
It'll be my treat.
I know a good hangover soup place nearby.
No, thanks.
Let's go.
Okay.
[grunts]
Thank you.
[car door closes]
About your arm.
You should get it checked.
Don't complain about it later.
Okay.
Thanks so much for everything today.
Text me your account details.
I'll wire you the gas--
[♪ whimsical music playing]
[sighs]
What is wrong with me?
Oh, whatever.
[groans]
It hurts.
[sighs in exasperation]
[♪ triumphant music playing on video]
[presenter over video] Where every step
and every breath carries elegance.
Where life becomes art.
[audience clapping]
It's Beauté Palace.
[employee 1] Beauté Department Store's
wedding festival
is for newlyweds
who want a great beginning.
A Beauté Palace unit
worth five million dollars
you just saw in the video
is the grand prize.
Yes, that's right.
It's Beauté Construction's
ambitious new project,
a high-end luxury town house.
It gathered a lot of attention,
and so many entered the raffle.
The couple that wins the apartment
must be so pleased.
I'd have delayed my wedding
if only I'd known.
I'm so sad I'm not a newlywed!
[all chuckle]
-Shall we pick the winners?
-Yes.
Everyone wants one of these at home.
A must-have
for the fashion-conscious, a styler!
Why make a huge fuss when it's rigged?
It must look real to avoid complaints.
You think?
I'm sure you took care of it.
[employee 2 over TV] Congratulations.
What do I do now?
[employee 2] One, zero,
seven, three!
Ha Minyeong, congratulations!
LEE SEONGGYU
DATE ENTERED: APRIL 12
Lee Seonggyu.
The mayor's wife's nephew?
Yes, that's right.
[♪ enthralling music playing]
[taps hand]
In case I get mixed up.
[audience clapping]
Beauté Department Store's
30th anniversary wedding festival.
It's time to select
the winner of the grand prize.
Let's not waste time and get right to it.
Beauté Department Store's CEO
will select the grand prize winner.
Sir! Come on up.
[audience cheering, clapping]
[all chuckle]
[♪ gripping music playing]
[employee 1] Our CEO is doing his best
to select the right winner.
Give him some applause!
[all cheering]
He picked a ticket at last.
The grand prize,
the Beauté Palace unit goes to...
Please announce the winner.
As the CEO of Beauté Department Store,
I will announce the winner myself.
The grand prize winner is...
[drum roll]
[♪ dramatic sting]
[vibrating]
[phone continues vibrating]
Hello?
Is this Ms. Yoo Meri?
This is Beauté Department Store's PR Team.
A raffle?
[grunts] What raffle do you mean?
2 MONTHS AGO
[Meri grunts]
Sorry.
WIN A TOWNHOUSE WORTH FIVE MILLION!
[♪ upbeat whimsical music playing]
YOO MERI
DATE ENTERED: APRIL 15
If I win,
I'll spend the rest of my life...
No, I'll do good even in the afterlife.
Oh, that.
I won?
What?
Yes.
Yes, that's me. I'm Yoo Meri.
Yes, of course. I'm sure it's me.
Congratulations, Ms. Yoo.
I need to confirm your identity.
Can you send us a few documents?
Oh, documents.
Yes, of course, I'll send them.
Give me a moment.
Yes, I'm ready.
[employee 1] A copy of your ID card.
A copy of my ID.
Proof that you don't own a home.
Proof that I don't own a home.
[employee 1] Proof of income,
and proof of marriage. That's it.
Proof of...
-Proof of marriage?
-Yes.
To be eligible to win, you must make
less than 80 million won a year
and be newlyweds who don't own a home.
Yes, okay. I understand.
Bye.
Proof of marriage?
Will they cancel my win
if I say I'm divorced?
[phone chimes]
I didn't hand that thing in.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
DIVORCE DECREE
I still have it.
Since I haven't handed it in yet...
FAMILY REGISTRATION DETAILS
SPOUSE: KIM WOOJU
I'm still legally married.
THIS DOCUMENT CERTIFIES THE ABOVE DETAILS
[gasps]
I checked everything thoroughly.
They're newlyweds
who got married five months ago,
don't own a home,
and their income meets the criteria, too.
She meets every requirement completely.
Shall we go ahead with the award ceremony?
Our CEO should attend as well.
-Postpone it for now.
-Okay.
What? To when?
[clicks tongue]
Well, Yoo Meri said
her husband couldn't come.
If we push back the ceremony,
I need to ask her if they'll be free.
Her husband can't come?
Why not?
I talked to her on the phone earlier.
Yes, I got all the documents.
Will your husband be abroad for a while?
Well...
I don't see why you can't come alone.
-That's a no.
-What?
Didn't you read the fine print?
[♪ dramatic music playing]
The fine print?
Yes, I just noticed the fine print
of the terms and conditions.
"The win will be canceled
if it turns out they lied
on any of the documents,
and the winner will be held
legally responsible."
And also...
"The winner must actively participate in
any company promotions,
and they must attend
the award ceremony as a couple."
That's a must.
There are no exceptions.
What?
You said earlier today
that it wouldn't matter.
Why the sudden change?
What happens if my husband can't make it?
Then it will be canceled.
It'll be canceled? That's not fair.
I won the raffle. You just need me.
Who cares if my husband's there or not?
That's the rule.
There's nothing I can do.
Ah!
[sighs]
CEO YOO MERI
Okay, I got it for now.
I'll be in touch.
What kind of rule is that?
This is madness.
[♪ pop music playing over speakers]
Give me a kiss.
-I love you.
-I love you, too.
MERI
[automated voice] To leave a message,
press one.
To leave your number, press two.
-[beep]
-Hello?
It's me. I can't seem to reach you.
I have something urgent to discuss.
Can you call me quickly?
It's really important.
I won a lucky draw kind of thing.
[♪ jazz music playing over speakers]
[exhales]
This is paradise.
Hey, baby.
You're back.
My cutie.
[both giggle]
Aren't you hungry?
-Are you hungry, Jenny?
-Yes.
-Shall we go eat?
[phone vibrates]
NEW MESSAGE
YOU HAVE A NEW VOICE MESSAGE
MERI
Who is it from?
It's a spam message.
[sighs]
BLOCK CONTACT
BLOCK
Let's go.
Okay.
WOOJU
[line ringing]
[automated voice]
The call cannot be connected.
Transferring to voicemail.
-[line disconnects]
-[exclaims]
Come on. Pick up.
I can't do anything
if I can't talk to you.
[♪ whimsical music playing]
It's as good as out of my reach.
It's a pie in the sky.
[phone vibrates]
This is Kim Wooju.
I was wondering if you went to the doctor.
No, I was too busy to...
NO, I WAS TOO BUSY TO
KIM WOOJU
[♪ dramatic guitar music playing]
WHERE LIFE BECOMES ART
KIM WOOJU
He has the same name.
The department store people
won't know if I bring someone else.
They've never seen him.
[♪ soft orchestral music playing
in background]
What did the doctor say?
Did you get a doctor's note?
Oh, the doctor.
I was too busy to see one.
Are you perhaps married?
I'm sorry?
Are you a married man?
No, why?
[chuckles nervously] That's a relief.
What is?
I gave it a lot of thought.
I know it's rash to say this
when we've only met once,
but you're the only one I can turn to.
Could you...
be my husband?
[♪ upbeat dreamy music playing]
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
WOULD YOU MARRY ME?
[Kim Wooju] You'll pay me
to play your fake husband
-for a day?
-[Meri] Yes.
[Kim Wooju] I'm not kind enough
to be generous to a scammer.
[assistant] The husband must be present.
Otherwise, we'll redraw.
-Are they in?
-[Songhee] They'll call after discussing.
[man] You quit as team leader if you fail.
[Meri] I lost everything in a rental con,
but I won a five-million-dollar house.
-I just need a husband to tag along.
-You won a prize?
So, that's what this is all about.
Do you have any idea
how risky this scam is?
It's me. How have you been?
I'm in Seoul.
I'm one of the residents here.
-Over there?
-That one?
Translated by Jennifer Jean Lim